BGM
Here we go, Apkami, this time with Kurumi Takase of Beyones Ame no Morikawa Umi and
and Yume from 17 Snacks.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at our two MCs.
I'm Kurumi Takase, and I've been working with Kisaki Ebata of Juice Juice and Rin Hashizaka of Angulum.
I had a chance to talk about dance with Kisaki Ebata of Juice Juice and Rin Hashizaka of Angulum.
At that time, Kisaki Ebata was asked by the choreographer to give a dance lesson and explain the process of choreography.
Kisaki Ebata was talking about how different choreographers give different dance lessons and choreograph the choreography.
Depending on the teacher, some teachers do all the choreography and positioning together, while others only do the choreography first and then put in the choreography.
some teachers do only the choreography first.
Okay.
Yes.
Some teachers teach the choreography first, and then teach the standing position after the choreography is done.
If you get too used to a teacher's way of doing things, you'll be surprised when a different teacher suddenly arrives.
If you get too used to the way of the teacher you are used to, you will be surprised when a different teacher suddenly arrives.
The other day, we had a chance to work with a new choreographer.
I had a chance to talk with the new choreographer.
And the choreographer himself was very interested in the idols and artists that he works with.
And the choreographer himself, depending on the idol or artist he's working with
I heard that the choreographer himself changes his approach according to the idols or artists he is in charge of, in order to make it easier for them to understand
I felt that they were intentionally changing things with us in mind.
It was a new discovery for me.
It was a new discovery for me, and I had an episode that gave me a fresh feeling.
I just learned about it for the first time.
I often have the same teacher choreograph my Juice Chus.
But I'm still very curious about it.
I would like to experience choreographing with many different choreographers.
As for me, Kudo...
I'm Kudo, and I've been having a problem with my shoes.
I recently realized why.
I wear the same shoes as my seniors.
But only my shoes have a high heel that comes off easily and becomes unstable.
I'm the only one who has a problem with sa-yeon-seok
Saeyeongseok
SAYEONSEOK
I was stretching my calves at the concert, wondering why
If the shoes were like this...
I stretched my calves in such a way that they shifted here like this.
The manager came up behind me and said
He said, "That's probably how high the temperature is.
He said, "That's how high the temperature is.
Yes, he did.
I realized that I was going to break my shoes by doing that.
From then on, I tried to be careful.
I'm really sorry.
I see.
But expensive shoes are more likely to break.
I actually do that move sometimes.
After hearing what you just said, I've decided not to do it anymore.
I really want to do my best to take care of my body while taking care of my shoes.
I'll be careful too.
Let's start with the Hello Project 25th Anniversary New Member Audition!
The audition for the new members of Hello Project's 25th anniversary was held at Karastenay and the successful candidates were announced.
A new member will join Tsubaki Factory!
Fuka Inoue, 13 years old, 2nd year junior high school student from Osaka. Yu Murado, 13 years old, 2nd year junior high school student from Aichi prefecture.
This is 15 year old junior high school student from Kanagawa prefecture.
I'm Fuka Inoue, a 13 year old junior high school student from Osaka, Japan. I'm 13 year old Iwami, a junior high school student from Kanagawa, Japan.
Thank you very much for your help!
Yes, it's nice to meet you!
I'm 15 years old and in my 3rd year of junior high school!
The photographer gave me a lot of advice this time.
I think I was able to move better than before.
I think I was able to move more than before.
I don't have many patterns, but I think I did the best I could.
I have been practicing a lot, and I hope it paid off.
I took dance lessons, so I'm better at that.
I don't have a specific genre in mind, as I have danced in all kinds of genres.
I've practiced a lot so far.
I've been practicing a lot, so I'm going to enjoy it and do my best so that I don't have any regrets.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, nice, that's great, OK
Oh, nice, good!
The end, huffing and puffing
OK, yeah, yeah, yeah
That's all the stuff that goes on.
So, are you crazy?
I'm Yu Murate, 13 years old, in the second year of junior high school.
At first, my expression was frozen or maybe...
But the photographer was very energetic.
He was very excited and said, "I like it, I like it!
I was so excited and had so much fun!
I'm used to making facial expressions at events because of my dance background.
I think I did a good job.
I'm confident because I used to choose songs that I thought I could do well, but
But this time, I chose a song that I am not good at, or rather, difficult to perform.
I've practiced a lot for that, so I'll do my best to show it.
I have a little confidence.
I'm good at jazz dance and K-pop.
I'm good at beautiful things.
I don't want to regret having come this far.
I've practiced hard, so I'll do my best to show it.
I'll do my best!
Coming soon!
Yes, sir.
Oh, wow, you're really good at posing.
Okay. Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There we go. There we go.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Ha-ha-ha.
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm 13 years old, Fuuka Doi, a second-year junior high school student from Osaka.
I was very nervous.
There were a lot of things I'm still getting used to, like posing.
I think I was able to do it.
I think I did.
I want to do my best to show what I've been working hard for.
I will do my best as myself.
I am better at dancing.
I will do my best to be myself and smile as much as I can.
I'm going to perform dance and sing to make everyone smile.
I will do my best to dance and sing to make everyone smile.
I will do my best.
I'm a little unstable and I'm a little emotional
change a little emotional instability good summer
I always want to be an ideal
I've got you, I've got you, I've got you
Everyday, Everynight
There's no such thing as cinematic romance
What's wrong with that? You're free to fantasize about anything you want
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
If only in your fantasy, you're free
I'm a strong princess
Sleepless Maiden, half past 1:30
Good night if you don't dream
BGM
We had a dance competition last time.
I think I was able to dance as hard as I could.
I danced while singing and sang only.
It was difficult.
I think I was able to show the result of my practice.
I was nervous, but it was a fun day.
I want to be an idol that everyone thinks my dancing is cool.
I want to be an idol that everyone thinks my dancing is cool!
Thank you for watching!
25 minutes later
Envimai Destiny's Journey to Unexplored Mountains
I'll read the coincidence before it happens, let's call up a miracle
Add up, add up, add up
How did we meet?
So add up, divide, and be guided
Envimai, a journey of destiny, an unexplored mountain
Let's seek more of life
Seek more happiness
I'm in a good mood
Even if it doesn't help
If you add it all up
If it makes you happy
I want you to laugh
Life support more and more and more
I'll ask for more and more
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching
Every day, every night is a cinematic romance.
What's wrong with that? Free to fantasize about being older, younger, lovey-dovey
Free if only in fantasy Free if only in fantasy I'm a strong princess
Sleepless rice, 1:30 Don't break the bank, you've got to dream
Gun Night
Thank you for watching
2 muscle failures
thank you for watching
When I was practicing, I was flipped over.
It was hard for me to do my voice.
But when I went to the voice training
I told him that I didn't make any mistakes in the show.
He told me that I would be twice as strong in the show.
I believed him, and I did it.
I was able to really give it my all without making any mistakes.
I got a good response.
I was so nervous before the show started, but
But when I was waiting and practicing
I became more and more calm.
And that gave me a little bit of confidence.
Now that it's over
I'm a little relieved.
I've been dancing for a long time.
I want to be an artist who can dance to the beat
I want to be an artist who can sing again
I also want to be able to bring a smile to people's faces.
Thank you for watching!
I didn't love you.
I won't give you a heartless kiss
I couldn't even sing to you
I couldn't sing
Pride, pride, pride
Only one and number one
No, no, no, look forward
Even for you
The pride I couldn't give you
No, no, no, look forward
I'll stay with you
Everyday, Everynight, Movie
It's a nice romance, isn't it?
What's wrong with that?
If you're paranoid, you're free
I'm older, I'm younger, I'm in love with you
I'm a strong princess
Sleeping maiden at half past
Gunnit if you don't dream
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching!
I was so nervous that my voice shook a little when I sang the song.
I want to do my best to sing well even when I'm nervous.
I made some mistakes.
I was able to do it in my own way.
I was very nervous at first, and I wasn't sure if I could do it.
But when I sang, I was so nervous.
I think I was able to sing and dance as if I could fly away from my nerves.
I want to be the kind of idol who can go to a lot of live performances and show my face of love and energy to my fans.
I want to be that kind of idol.
Thank you very much for your hard work!
Now you've seen how the auditions went!
The successful candidate for the Hello Project 25th Anniversary New Member Audition is...
Miu Ishii, a 15-year-old junior high school student from Kanagawa Prefecture
Yu Murata, 13 years old, 2nd year junior high school student, from Aichi Prefecture
Fuka Doi, a 13-year-old 2nd year junior high school student from Osaka
We are pleased to announce that they will be joining Tsubaki Factory as new members!
Congratulations!
It's too good to be true!
Hey...
You know...
The third one at the end...
She said she had no experience in dancing or singing.
I was wondering if she really had no experience.
as if she really had no experience.
Everyone really put a lot of effort into it.
I could tell that they had put a lot of effort into it.
I could tell that they had practiced a lot.
I thought it was amazing.
In my opinion
I thought that Yu Murata-chan
chose Beyond's music
as the song for the assignment.
I don't know...
I'm not really good at it.
I'm not really good at it, but she said she chose
He said that he was willing to try something like that
in the second year of junior high school
It's amazing that you already have that.
and that
I was also very happy that the song they tried was their own
I was also very happy that the song
and
Miu Ishii is also very good at taking pictures
When she was small
I could see that she was a little bit nervous
but when I saw her singing and dancing
I saw her singing and dancing, she looked so confident.
I thought, "You said you were nervous.
The way your hair was flowing was so cool.
I'm looking forward to seeing more and more cool ways to showcase your talent.
I'm really looking forward to it!
That's all about the audition for the new members of Hello Project
Hello Project 25th Anniversary New Member Audition!
Thank you for all your hard work!
Next, here it is!
Juice Juice Wonderful World 2023 Juice Juice Ver. Vocal Recording
From Juice Juice's latest album
Here is the vocal recording of Akari Endo from Juice Juice Wonderful World 2023 Juice Juice Ver.
Okay, let's get started. First of all, I'm going to do the head part later, so let's leave that for now.
So let's start with the first chorus. Yes, please.
This world is wonderful, isn't it?
When I think of you
This is a Wonderful World
Yes, yes, first of all, this world is wonderful
This World is Wonderful
This world is wonderful
With you, when I think of you
This is a Wonderful World
Here, the notes get pretty low.
At the end of the chorus, really at the end of the song, I want to end on a brighter note, so I'm going to sing as brightly as possible.
It's on pitch, so try to sing it as brightly as you can.
Try to sing as brightly as possible.
It's going to be on pitch, so I'm going to sing it as brightly as I can
It's a wonderful world, isn't it?
More than I thought it would be when you're here
When I think of you when you're here
This is a Wonderful World
OK
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's go to number two.
Because we met
This world is
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Thank you for watching.
Life is regenerative.
It's a beautiful world, isn't it?
It's that feeling.
And the "because we met" part...
I don't mean "because we met".
Because we met.
Yes, yes, yes, note by note, pretty firmly.
Yes, yes, yes.
OK, so that's how it was.
Jean Seiwa, you know, you're pretty high in the head.
I'll put "Gene" in the head.
Gene Seiwa
Gene Seiwa.
It doesn't matter if you miss a few notes, just make sure you get them in there.
Try your best.
OK, let's try one more time.
Yes, please.
This world is so beautiful because we met.
Teya!
Life is fine
Life's a little bit out of fashion right now, thank you very much.
It's a beautiful day.
Just like the high school word.
It's getting cloudy while I'm saying it's sunny!
It's going to be sunny. It's going to be ridiculously bright.
That's about it. That's all.
The rest was great.
Life is fine. Let's do six shots.
Let's do six rounds of this.
Life is a rebirth.
Okay.
Then let's try the door head.
This world's great, isn't it?
I was thinking we should all do the chorus.
Endos, let's hear you sing the part above the chorus
It's a wonderful world, isn't it?
So much love.
Okay, okay. Thank you very much.
Okay, thank you. That's all for now. Thank you very much.
Yes, this version was newly re-recorded as a silek, but the song layout was the same as the original live performance, so we had to record parts of the song.
Akari is still in her third year of junior high school, so she has a very adult-like atmosphere, but there are some babyish parts that I think are really cute.
When I first heard this song, the first part of the chorus was newly added and I was really impressed by it.
I was really impressed by that.
I was really moved by the fact that it was a song from a PsyRecording album, and the fact that Akari Uemura's voice, who was a member of Wonderful World when it was released, was there, and the voices of the other members who came in with the passage of time, so it's the same song, but it sounds different. It's the same song, but it's a different song.
It's a little bit like the fans are looking at the song from the perspective of a release.
I know it sounds a little bit like a release from a fan's point of view, but I think it's very moving and, at the risk of sounding a bit clichéd, I think it's very emo.
That's right.
I was very happy to be able to see the production process of this song because I feel a thrill every time I listen to it.
That's all for now, juice juice juice!
Wonderful World 2023 Juice Juice Version
Akari Endo's Walkal Recording!
Let's watch the rest together!
Beyones, Rain Forest, River Sea with Kurumi Takase
Choo Choo Snack Dough Princess is presenting this aapkomi!
Here's the next one!
Morning Musume。23 Makeup Call Wake Up When You Wake Up Vocal Recording
From Morning Musume。23's latest single, "Makeup Call: When You Wake Up".
Makeup Call: When You Wake Up, please take a look at the vocal recording of Rena Yokoyama!
Okay, let's do it in block blocks, starting from the first A melody in order.
Okay, let's start from the A melody of the first number and do it in a block block.
I thought I'd try to be a little cool here.
A little blunt.
That kind of makeup doesn't suit you.
The discipline of femininity without being gussa
The way she sings
A little bit of rock taste
music
That kind of makeup doesn't suit you
Imposition of unquenchable femininity
It's not for love, it's not for love, it's not for love
That's all I'm trying to say
OK, then
I'm going to be your junior.
I'm not in it for you, I'm in it for love. That's all I'm saying.
Cute, cool, stable, love-conscious.
I'm a creature with a line for love. I have to affirm every face.
You have to say it in your own voice, no matter what you look like, and then it's spring.
It's a little more difficult than that.
Try a little harder.
Also, the first four lines of "cute," I wanted to accentuate the head.
"Cute, cool, mocking, and vivid.
Be a little conscious of that.
I was thinking I'd change the split here.
I changed it from cute, cool, mawkish, and aimlessly a little bit to cute, cool, mawkish, and aimlessly a little bit.
I thought I'd change the character a little bit, like "cute, cool, mawkish, and aimlessly a little bit".
I thought I'd change the character a little bit.
Cute, cool, charming, and a little bit fake and a little bit fake and a little bit fake and a little bit fake and a little bit fake.
Couldn't he be more mocking?
Mawkishly...
Mawkishly and a little bit...
It's hard, isn't it?
Let's try again.
Please.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I want to say.
Cute, cool, anzaiyaku, and sincere.
Okay, let's try the B melody.
A little more triplets at the top.
Feel it as you sing it.
The last line...
It was good now, but you should sing it a little thicker
I don't want to...
I don't want you to cheat me
WAKE UP
to the last line
It just flows into the song? Yes.
So, let's try it once. Yes, please.
A creature with a tortoise's line. I have to affirm any face.
I'm sure it's boring to leave it to others This thought that I decide for myself is unshakable
I, you know, don't want to deceive me WAKE UP
OK, let's move on.
Rhythm 1.
I don't want to deceive myself
Wake up call It's time to wake up, it's time to enjoy life
The sun is in my heart Do it!
I'll light it up Dance baby Dance baby Dance baby Dance baby
I tried to be as cool as possible
But it's also a little weird, a little strong
A little bit weird, a little bit strong, a little bit cool
A little bit peculiar, a little bit strong
Yes, yes, yes, yes, it's a little bit peculiar
Who's singing this? I thought it would be okay to say something like "Who's singing this?
Okay, I understand.
Okay, let's try it.
Dir umler
It's time. The sun is in my heart
Just do it just do it just do it just do it
I'll shine my light on you
Dance baby dance baby dance baby dance baby
Okay, I just took it off
There in the night
I was thinking about going to Falu earlier.
That's what I'm talking about.
I want to be cool there at night.
I'm going to be cool there at night
Someone's heart is waiting for the morning.
I want to step things up a bit there, too.
Yes, sir.
The sun is in this heart
Just do it Just do it Just do it Just do it
Someone's heart at the bottom of the night waiting for morning
I'll come out
OK
You're downstairs now, right?
Let's make it sound as good as we can
I'll try to use a thicker voice
Just do it Just do it Just do it Just do it
Someone's heart at the bottom of the night waiting for morning
I'm coming out
Surprisingly wide range
I can do both.
I think I'll do one of these with double kanji.
Jean to we.
Someone's heart waiting for morning at the bottom of the night
OK, I got it!
So it looks like we got all of them.
Okay!
Then we're done!
Thank you very much!
When I listen to the recording of this song, I can't help but feel that the song has a fast-paced feel to it.
I love the way Yokoyama-san's facial expression comes out when he sings.
When I listen to the CD, I can't see the expressions on their faces, but when I hear Yokoyama's voice, I can really picture their expressions.
I was very happy to see the recording video.
I haven't had a chance to see the director's recording yet, but I hope to have a chance to see it someday.
I've never had a recording session with the director, but I'd like to have one someday.
I want to be excited and meet a new me.
I would like to meet a new me.
Lyons is often directed by this director.
It was really interesting to see how other groups were following the same atmosphere.
There was an order in the middle of the show to make it more habitual and strong in flavor, right?
That's still there, isn't it?
Beyoncé is often told that.
I've been told that a lot, and the result is that the songs have a strong flavor now.
I'm glad to know that the recording process is the same.
I'm also happy to know that the recording process is the same, and that even with the same kind of direction, it depends on the person or the group.
I was also happy to know that the recording process was the same, and I was also amazed to see how the song turned out differently depending on the person or group who took the same direction.
I thought that was also interesting.
That's all for this Morning Musume。23 wake up callWake up when you wake upVocal Recording of Rena Yokoyama
Thank you for watching!
Ocha no oma! First album Channel 1 is now on sale!
I'm sure you'll be fine as usual
It's time to say goodbye to Apkami, brought to you by Kurumi Takase and Yume Kudo!
We have seen a lot of footage this time.
We've seen a lot of videos this time, but we were able to see the precious audition video that will remain in the history of the company.
I was very happy to be able to see the historic and precious audition video first hand.
Dance auditions are filled with various dances and genres, and I think there were some genres that I was not good at.
I think there were some genres that I was not good at.
I think it would be terrifying if I could audition for those genres, so I was really happy to see the members who could do it.
I thought it was really cool that the members were able to do that.
It was a very inspiring episode for me.
I'm sure that Tsubaki Factory will be able to do it again with the new members.
I'm sure that Tsubaki Factory will also have a new history
I'm really looking forward to seeing the new members come in and add new colors to Tsubaki Factory.
Whenever I see a video of new members like this, it reminds me of my own beginnings.
I was reminded of my own initial feelings when I saw these images of new members.
At the time of my audition
I was so nervous and my face was so stiff.
I must have been so nervous that my face was stiff.
I can go back to the beginning of my life.
I think it's a place where I can go back to the basics, so I need to go back to the basics too.
I'd like to do my best to keep my original intention in mind.
And in the future, I'd like to talk with the three members of Shmeva at Hello Project concerts.
I'm looking forward to talking and performing with the three members of Shumeva at Hello Project concerts and other events.
At the end of the day, I'm looking forward to talking and performing with the three members of Shumeba at the Upfront Group concerts.
We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of the various artists who belong to the Upfront Group.
We'll be showing you what you don't normally see, so please subscribe to our channel!
Please subscribe to our channel!
This time, we'll be talking with
Kurumi Takase of Beyons, Amenomori, and Kawawumi
and Yume Kudo of Chus Chus.
Farewell.
In the next episode, we will be showing the recording of Tsubaki Factory's "Atarizumu" and the hair arrangement of a member from Angulum. Please look forward to it!